

# LISA ISELIN

## **UI** Designer Graphic Designer

lisaiselin.com

UI designer, strategic thinker, and optimistic team player with an innate sense of empathy and 10 years of graphic design experience. A self-motivated human with contagiously positive energy, and a never-ending eagerness to learn. Enthusiastically dead-set on having fun and becoming part of a growing team achieving greatness.



#### Contact

303.725.4769

lisaiselin@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/lisaiselin



lisaiselin.com/contact



### Skills & Tools

#### { Hard Skills }

- UI/UX Design
- Visual & Graphic Design
- Interactive Responsive Design
- Brand Identity & Development
- Functional Pixel-Perfect Designs
- Photo & Creative Art Direction

#### { Soft Skills }

- Collaborative & Team-Oriented
- Self-Motivated
- Integrity
- Empathy
- Analytical Mindset
- Eager to Learn
- Time & Project Management
- Adaptable
- Process-Oriented

- Wireframes
- Problem Solving
- Prototypes & Mockups
- Research & User Testing
- Competitor Analysis
- User Flows & Info. Architecture

#### { **Tools** }

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- InVision
- GitHub
- Atom
- HTML5 & CSS3



### Education

## **CareerFoundry**

- UI Design Immersion Certificate
- Frontend Dev Specialization Certificate

## University of Minnesota

- B.S.: Graphic Design
- Emphasis : Advertising



#### **Hobbies**





Ride }





Sip



 $\supset \{Run\}$ 



# Experience

## { Organic Return }

- · Website design for real estate brokerage clients, including, new concept creation, design utilizing existing style guides, and creative
- Research, identification of user problems, wireframes, and visual design
- Print and digital design including brochures, flyers, and banners
- · Organic Return company rebrand

UI Designer | 2021-Present

## Consulting & Freelance Designer | 2012–Present { Iselin Design }

• UI/UX, visual design, and branding for digital marketing agency, social media startup, performance consulting, chiropractic clinics, non-profit, manufacturing, and lab equipment supplier for higher education markets

## *UI/UX Designer* | 2021–2022

#### { Journey }

- · Redesign of native mobile app notifications center
- Creation of user payment gateway for Journey web app
- Landing page design for Journey website
- · Conducted design audit of onboarding flow with recommendations to improve onboarding conversion rate
- Experience with design systems, variant creation, and style guides
- · Worked directly with CEO, developers, designers, and marketing

## Graphic Designer | 2017–2020

#### { Globus }

- Print and digital design including emails, digital banners, social media, trade show collateral, ads, packaging, billboards, invites, and small animations
- Upheld creative and brand standards on all collateral for 4 different Globus sub-brands targeting both direct and B2B customers
- Collaborated cross-functionally, and with B2B partners

# Production Manager | 2016–2017

### { Dish Network }

- Developed and managed Production Team designers
- · Upheld corporate brand standards, maintaining quality assurance of all Production Team projects

## Art Director | 2012–2016

#### { Sports Authority }

- Led and directed Creative Team through entire creative process, concept, design, development, and execution of projects, brand and quarterly campaigns, style guide development, and photoshoots
- Collaborated and communicated cross-functionally, completing creatively aligned projects and deliverables in an efficient time frame